ZIQI FANG

San Leandro 94579, CA · 8313311279

zfang1207@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/ziqi-fang: · ziqifang-portfolio.com

Computer Science graduate specialized in front-end development with proficiency in React.js and modern web technologies. Committed to crafting responsive and engaging user interfaces and adept at translating design into functional user experiences.

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2024 - JULY 2024

DATA ANALYST INTERN, ELDON GROUP

Prepare reports for internal and external audiences using business analytics reporting tools. Analyzing and reporting results back to the business or the management team to establish business needs.

DECEMBER 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2023

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN, YUQING EDUCATION

Developed front-end components of a school management system, enhancing user interactivity and engagement.

EDUCATION

DECEMBER 2022

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA,

SANTA CRUZ

Cumulative GPA: 3.7 | Honors: Dean's Honor List & Dean's Award (2019-2022)

SKILLS

- Programing Languages: Python, JavaScript
- UI / UX Design tools: Figma
- Web Dev Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Next.js
- DevOps Cycle & Cloud Services: AWS Cloud Services, Git, GitHub, CI/CD, Agile Methodologies
- Data Analysis: SQL, Relational Database, Spreadsheet, Excel, Python analytic tools (Pandas etc.)

CERTIFICATES

FEBRUARY 2023

AWS CERTIFIED CLOUD PRACTITIONER, AMAZON WEB SERVICES

Certification link: AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Badge Page

(https://www.credly.com/badges/525e2769-6fe8-4aca-81cb-a8f19a3c2336/public_url)

AUGUST 2023

AWS SOLUTION ARCHITECT ASSOCIATE, AMAZON WEB SERVICES

Certification link: AWS Cloud Solution Architect Associate Certificate Badge Page

(https://www.credly.com/badges/3d2fd7e1-3602-4c79-89a4-a18d681663b4/public_url)

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

CHATPDF (WEB-BASED SAAS APPLICATION)

- Production site link: https://chat-pdf-pied-psi.vercel.app/
- Pioneered an Al-driven chatbot application, enhancing user engagement with PDF content.
- Executed full-stack development using Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, and React.js.
- Designed a seamless user interface with Tailwind CSS and Shadon, ensuring intuitive UX.
- Orchestrated user data management with DrizzleORM, NeonDB, and MongoDB.
- Integrated Stripe API for subscription-based revenue model and Clerk Auth for user authentication

SUSHIER (WEB-BASED E-COMMERCE PROJECT)

- Production site link: https://www.sushier.app
- Developed a responsive E-commerce web application using React.js, Tailwind CSS and Next.js
- Implemented robust user authentication with NextAuth and RESTful API with Node.js and Express.js.

ONLINE PRESENCE & CONTRIBUTIONS

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE: HTTP://ZIQIFANG-PORTFOLIO.COM

YOUTUBE CHANNEL:

HTTP://YOUTUBE.COM/CHANNEL/UCXV5XX0QCXRW9YA4EMNHULQ

GITHUB REPOSITORY: HTTP://GITHUB.COM/SHERRYFANG1207

LANGUAGES

• English: Fluent

Chinese: Native

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- GRE (Graduate Records Examination) Test: 328 + 4
- Working Permission: No sponsor needed. Available to start work at any time.